University Advancement fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Alumni Relations Office, 1968 - 2015; F-53-4; 32 cm of textual records
  - AQ, Vol. 8, 2007; F-53-4-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - AQ, Vol. 9, 2008; F-53-4-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 53-10)
  - AQ, Vol. 10, 2009; F-53-4-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 53-12)
  - AQ, Vol. 11, 2010; F-53-4-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 53-12)
  - AQ, Vol. 12, 2011; F-53-4-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 53-12)
  - AQ, Vol. 13, 2012; F-53-4-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 53-12)
  - AQ, Vol. 14, 2013; F-53-4-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 53-12)
  - AQ, Vol. 15, 2014; F-53-4-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 53-12)
  - AQ, Vol. 16, 2015; F-53-4-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 53-12)